[music]
I hope you [music] like me.
If you do, I like you, too.
Why don't you [music] try me?
I'm lost when I'm with you.
>> [music]
>> I don't know if you share this light and
[music] think about you late [singing]
at night.
I'm wondering [music] if this feeling
is
true.
I hope we're more [music] than just
friends.
I hope you feel this, too.
I hope I'm more than just friends.
I [music] want to be with you.
What if you say no?
But what if [music] you say yes I do?
Tired of laying low. I'm lost when I'm
with you. [music]
I don't know if you share this light.
Think about you late at night. [music]
I'm wondering if this feeling
is
true. [music]
I hope I'm more than just friends.
I hope you feel this, [music] too.
I want to be [music] with you.
I hope I'm more than just friends.
I hope you feel this, too. [music]
I hope for more than just
I want to be with [music] you.
I hope you feel
I just friends. [music]
I want to be with you.
I hope more than just friends.